Finding aid for the Jane Sedgwick Papers
Medical Heritage Center
- Series IV: People (5 boxes) documents people who work or worked in the medical center. The series is arranged alphabetically by a person's last name., 1943-1999
  - Evans, William, 1970-1973 (Box 7, Folder 111)
  - Eyring, Edward J., 1967-1972 (Box 7, Folder 112)
  - Fahey, Patrick J. -RESTRICTED, 1986-1988 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Falko, James M., 1985-1987 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Farrar, William -RESTRICTED, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Fass, Robert J., 1971-1980 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Ferguson, Ronald M. -RESTRICTED, 1982-1993 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Ferris, Thomas F., 1967-1976 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Fertel, Richard, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Fischer, Roland, 1961-1967 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Folk, Robert L., 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Fontana, Mary, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Fox, Ronald E., 1968-1973 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Frajola, Walter J., 1959-1961 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Freedy, Lucy, 1986-1988 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Freimanis, Atis K., 1961-1983 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Fritz, Edna L., 1973-1983 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Fromkes, John J. -RESTRICTED, 1980-1987 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Fry, Donald, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Fryczkowski, Andrzej, 1992-1993 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Fulkerson, Philip, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Gabbe, Steven G. -RESTRICTED, 1986-1990 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Gadek, James E., 1982-1987 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Gahbauer, Reinhart, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Galbraith, Timothy A., 1986 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Gaughran, George R. L., 1961-1985 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Geer, Jack Charles, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - George, Jack, 1967-1987 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Gerber, Nicholas, 1983-1989 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Gibson, William M., 1964 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Glaser, Ronald, 1977-1993 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Gogate, Shashikala, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Goodman, Joseph, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Goodman, Richard M., 1965-1971 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Goorey, Louis J., 1992 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Graham, Bruce D., 1964-1976 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Grant, Helen Kay, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Gray, Linda Sue -RESTRICTED, No Date (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Gregory, Ian, 1965-1985 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Grossie, James Allen, 1965-1979 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Guralnick, Michael J., 1975-1977 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Gwynne, Peter, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Haas, Adolph, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Hackshaw, Kevin, No Date (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Hahn, George, 1981-1986 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Hall, William L., 1986 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Hammar, Carl Gustaf V., 1978 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Hamparian, Vincent V., 1964-1975 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Hanson, Kenneth Marvin, 1966-1976 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Harding, Frances Keller, 1965-1974 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Harris, Randall, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Hartley, Ronald B., 1971 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Hauser, Peggy, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Havener, William, 1954-1991 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Hayes, Thomas G., 1974-1983 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Haynes, Ralph, 1967-1987 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Hebert, Lee -RESTRICTED, 1981-1989 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Hendrich, Chester E., 1968 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Henry, Mitchell, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Hiatt, Edwin P., 1960-1973 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Hill, Stephen, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Hille, Russ, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Hines, Margaret (Peg), 1971-1988 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Hodgson, Sheila -RESTRICTED, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Hollander, Philip, 1964-1977 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Hollenbeck, Zeph J. R., 1974-1987 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Holzaepfel, John H., 1970 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Horrocks, Lloyd A., 1968-1974 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Hosier, Donald M., 1954-1988 (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Hostetler, Jepeth, 1972-1989 (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Huddleston, Jerry, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - Hunt, William, 1973-1986 (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Hunter, William, 1972-1987 (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - Jackson, Rebecca, 1982-1990 (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - James, Arthur, 1956-1987 (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - Jesseph, John -RESTRICTED, 1965-1971 (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Johnson, Charles, 1981-1988 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Johnson, Ernest -RESTRICTED, 1962-1992 (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Johnson, Ernest, 1962-1992 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Johnson, George Odin, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Johnson, J. David, 1985-1988 (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - Jonasson, Olga, 1987-1992 (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - Kaeding, Christopher, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Kangas, John, 1966-1973 (Box 8, Folder 82)
  - Kantor, Seth -RESTRICTED, 1985-1987 (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - Kaplan, Paul, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 84)
  - Kapoor, Neena, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 85)
  - Kapral, Frank A., 1966-1972 (Box 8, Folder 86)
  - Kartha, Mukund K., 1969 (Box 8, Folder 87)
  - Kaufman, Russel E., 1993 (Box 8, Folder 88)
  - Keates, Richard, 1968-1988 (Box 8, Folder 89)
  - Keith, Luther, 1968-1987 (Box 8, Folder 90)
  - Kelley, Curtin, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 91)
  - Kelley, Stephen, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 92)
  - Keller, Martin -RESTRICTED, 1966-1988 (Box 8, Folder 93)
  - Kennedy, Melanie Sproul -RESTRICTED, 1978-1985 (Box 8, Folder 94)
  - Kiecolt-Glaser, Janice, 1984-1986 (Box 8, Folder 95)
  - Kien, C. Lawrence -RESTRICTED, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 96)
  - Kilman, James -RESTRICTED, 1965-1976 (Box 8, Folder 97)
  - Kim, Moon -RESTRICTED, 1977-1992 (Box 8, Folder 98)
  - King, James Sargent, 1975-1993 (Box 8, Folder 99)
  - King, John, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 100)
  - Kissel, John, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 101)
  - Klassen, Karl P., 1957-1979 (Box 8, Folder 102)
  - Klainer, Albert S., 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 103)
  - Knopp, Walter & Lisa, 1967-1981 (Box 8, Folder 104)
  - Koizumu, Hisako, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 105)
  - Koranyi, Katalini, 1971-1979 (Box 8, Folder 106)
  - Krauss, Herbert, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 107)
  - Kraut, Eric, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 108)
  - Kruger, Fred, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 109)
  - Kunin, Calvin, 1979-1982 (Box 8, Folder 110)
  - Kunz, Albert, 1965-1982 (Box 8, Folder 111)
  - Lamberson, John, No Date (Box 8, Folder 112)
  - Lang, Raymond W., 1968 (Box 8, Folder 113)
  - Leake, Chauncey, 1960-1978 (Box 8, Folder 114)
  - LeBrie, Stephen, 1966-1970 (Box 8, Folder 115)
  - Leier, Carl V., 1982-1992 (Box 8, Folder 116)
  - Lembach, Richard, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 117)
  - Lessler, Milton, 1961-1985 (Box 8, Folder 118)
  - Lewis, Richard P., 1969-1982 (Box 8, Folder 119)
  - Lim, David (Jong Jai), 1967-1985 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Lindower, John -RESTRICTED, 1970-1978 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Lipsky, Joseph, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Liss, Leopold -RESTRICTED, 1960-1987 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Little, Robert, 1965-1972 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Lo Buglio, Albert, 1969-1983 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Loebs, Stephen, 1980-1992 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Lombardo, John, 1991-1993 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Lott, John, 1968-1987 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Lowery, Brian, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Lowney, Edmund, 1969-1985 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Lubow, Martin, 1968-1969 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - MacLean, Ian, 1967-1972 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Macpherson, Colin, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Malarkey, William, 1981-1987 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Marks, Bernard, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Marks, Philip A., 1966 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Martin, George, 1973-1991 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Martin, Ted -RESTRICTED, 1985-1987 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Martinek, John, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Matkovic, Veumir, No Date (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Mavissakalian, Matig -RESTRICTED, 1986-1988 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Maxwell, Robert, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Mazzaferri, Ernest -RESTRICTED, 1976-1992 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - McCluer, Robert H., 1968 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - McClung, H. Juhling, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - McCoy, Francis, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - McDonald, John S., 1978-1982 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - McEnany, M. Terry, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - McNeil, Donald, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Meagher, John N., 1968-1971 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Meckstroth, Charles -RESTRICTED, 1967-1988 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Meiling, Richard, 1954-1986 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Meiling, Richard, 1954-1986 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Meiling, Richard, 1960-1984 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Meites, Samuel, No Date (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Mekhjian, Hagop S. -RESTRICTED, 1970-1993 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Meleca, C. Benjamin, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Melnick, William, 1975-1981 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Melvin, John, 1960-1973 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Mendell, Jerry, 1982-1992 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Merola, John, 1966-1990 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Metz, Earl N., 1968-1985 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Miglets, Andrew W., 1975-1983 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Miller, Carole, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Milo, George E., 1980 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Minton, John Peter, 1975-1990 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Missildine, W. Hugh, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Molleson, Ann, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Molnar, William, 1954-1988 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Monroe, Lawrence J., 1969 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Moodispaw, Paul, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Morris, J. Douglas, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Morris, Leibert, 1985-1987 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Morrow III, Grant -RESTRICTED, 1978-1993 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Mueller, Charles, 1977-1989 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Murphy, Robert J., 1979-1991 (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Myerowitz, P. David, 1986-1991 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Myers, William G., 1953-1988 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Nagi, Saad, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Nasrallah, Henry A., 1985-1990 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Neff, John -RESTRICTED, 1980-1986 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Neff, Maria, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Neff, Norton, 1984-1990 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Negulesco, John, 1982-1991 (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - Neidhart, James, 1978-1981 (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - Nelson, Carl E., 1966 (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - Newman, Howard A., 1969-1979 (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - Newton, William A., 1966 (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - Nilo, Ernest, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - Nishikawara, Margaret, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - Noyes, David H., 1969 (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - Nuenke, Richard H., 1962-1978 (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - Nutt, Paul, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - O'Donnell, Frank, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - O'Dorisio, Sue Wedemeyer -RESTRICTED, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 76)
  - O'Dorisio, Thomas M. -RESTRICTED, 1975-1988 (Box 9, Folder 77)
  - O'Neill, John, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 78)
  - O'Shaughnessy, Richard, 1978-1980 (Box 9, Folder 79)
  - Och, Fern, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 80)
  - Olsen, John -RESTRICTED, 1987-1991 (Box 9, Folder 81)
  - Osei, Kwame -RESTRICTED, 1985-1987 (Box 9, Folder 82)
  - Ostrum, Robert, 1988-1990 (Box 9, Folder 83)
  - Ottolenghi, Abramo C., 1967-1992 (Box 9, Folder 84)
  - Pace, William III, 1963-1970 (Box 9, Folder 85)
  - Panganamala, Rao, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 86)
  - Para, Michael F., 1987-1993 (Box 9, Folder 87)
  - Pariser, Stephen F., 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 88)
  - Parris, Deborah, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 89)
  - Paul, Lawrence, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 90)
  - Paul, Leonard -RESTRICTED, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 91)
  - Paulson, George, 1967-1982 (Box 9, Folder 92)
  - Pease, William, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 93)
  - Perkins, Robert L., 1971-1982 (Box 9, Folder 94)
  - Pieper, Heinz P. -RESTRICTED, 1961-1985 (Box 9, Folder 95)
  - Pierson, Frank, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 96)
  - Pintz, Evelyn, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 97)
  - Pluoffe, Joseph, 1981-1987 (Box 9, Folder 98)
  - Pollack, J. Dennis, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 99)
  - Powell, Dwight, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 100)
  - Prior, John A., 1964-1992 (Box 9, Folder 101)
  - Pyant, Kathryn, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 102)
  - Rall, Jack, 1984-1986 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Rammohan, Kottil, 1982-1983 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Reiss, Rosemary, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Reynolds, Ann W., 1970s-1979 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Richardson, Keith, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Rie, Herbert, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Rieske, John S., 1966-1975 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Rigsby, Willian C., 1966 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Rinehart, John, 1980-1985 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Robinson, John, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Rogers, Richard, 1986-1989 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Rotter, Andrej -RESTICTED, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Ruberg, Robert L., 1981-1991 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Rund, Douglas, 1977-1992 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Ruppert, Richard and Elizabeth, 1964-1977 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Russell, Orville E., 1973 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Ruyman, Fred, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Ryan, Joseph, 1966-1986 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Samuels, Larry, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Saslaw, Samuel, 1966-1976 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Saunders, William, 1961-1988 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Sayers, Martin P., 1980-1985 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Schaal, Stephen, 1970-1988 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Schiller, Rositta, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Schoen, Kathryn T., 1967-1983 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Schofield, Earl Clyde, 1954-1955 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Schuller, David, 1984-1991 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Schumm, Dorothy, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Season, Edwin H., 1970-1976 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Senhauser, Donald, 1975-1992 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Shaffer, Thomas E., 1954-1975 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Sharma, Hari, 1980-1988 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Shepard, William Frederick, 1956-1979 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Sherard, Earl S., 1968-1983 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Sherburne, Clifford C., 1959 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Shillito, Frederick H., 1960-1986 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Shinowara, George Y., 1955-1972 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Shirk, Frieda I., 1970 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Shuttleworth, Edwin C., Jr., 1974-1985 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Shy, Kathy, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Sills, Grayce M., 1968-1972 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Simon, Sheldon, 1986-1988 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Sirak, Howard D., 1958-1967 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Skillman, Thomas G., 1967-1993 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Skitarelic, Kathryn, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Slivka, Andrew, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Smead, William L., 1979-1987 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Smith, Blanca, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Smith, Charles W., 1969-1988 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Smith, Jack, 1985-1988 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Somerson, Norman L., 1966-1975 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Sotes, Juan, 1967-1971 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Sparkman, Marjorie F., 1969 (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Speicher, Carl, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Spigos, Dimitrious G., 1993 (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Sprecher, Howard William, 1964-1982 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - St. Pierre, Ronald L., 1968-1983 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Stang, John M., 1975-1987 (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Stein, David S., 1985 (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Stein, Jay H., 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Stephens, Ralph, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Stephens, Robert, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Stevens, Vernon C., 1980-1985 (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Stevenson, Thomas D., 1968 (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - Stilson, Alden E., Jr., 1960 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Stokes, Bradford T., 1977-1985 (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - Stoner, Clinton Dale, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - Stow, Richard W., 1972-1978 (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - Strauch, Arthur R., 1991 (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - Strauss, Richard, 1984-1986 (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - Sucheston, Martha W., 1974-1989 (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - Suie, Ted, 1968-1983 (Box 10, Folder 72)
  - Sullivan, Michael J., 1991 (Box 10, Folder 73)
  - Taylor, Jack, No Date (Box 10, Folder 74)
  - Temple, Patricia, No Date (Box 10, Folder 75)
  - Teske, Douglas, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 76)
  - Teteris, Nicholas J., 1961-1970 (Box 10, Folder 77)
  - Thomas, Fred B., 1975-1977 (Box 10, Folder 78)
  - Thomford, Neil Roger, 1966-1973 (Box 10, Folder 79)
  - Tomashefski, Joseph F., 1960-1967 (Box 10, Folder 80)
  - Tompkins, Ronald B., 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 81)
  - Torello, Michael M., 1986 (Box 10, Folder 82)
  - Townshend, William A., 1969 (Box 10, Folder 83)
  - Townsley, John D., 1968 (Box 10, Folder 84)
  - Trewyn, Ronald W., 1988 (Box 10, Folder 85)
  - Trzebiatowski, Gregory, 1969-1986 (Box 10, Folder 86)
  - Turner, Edward V., 1968-1975 (Box 10, Folder 87)
  - Turner, Harry Spencer, 1968-1970 (Box 10, Folder 88)
  - Tutschka, Peter Josef, 1983-1987 (Box 10, Folder 89)
  - Tzagournis, Manuel, 1960-1999 (Box 10, Folder 90)
  - Tzagournis, Manuel (Photographs), No Date (Box 10, Folder 91)
  - Ullery, John C., 1954-1968 (Box 10, Folder 92)
  - Unrerferth, Don V., 1970-1988 (Box 10, Folder 93)
  - Vaccaro, Patrick, 1980-1988 (Box 10, Folder 94)
  - Vasko, John S., 1966-1982 (Box 10, Folder 95)
  - Vermeule, Victor Richard, Jr., 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 96)
  - Vernall, Donald G., 1980-1986 (Box 10, Folder 97)
  - Vincent, Donald J., 1979-1982 (Box 10, Folder 98)
  - Von Haam, Emmerich, 1955-1988 (Box 10, Folder 99)
  - Wall, Robert L., 1962-2001 (Box 10, Folder 100)
  - Walson, Phillip D., 1981 (Box 10, Folder 101)
  - Ward, Patrick E., 1988 (Box 10, Folder 102)
  - Warmolts, John, 1981-1988 (Box 10, Folder 103)
  - Warren, James V. I (Pictures), 1952-1988 (Box 10, Folder 104)
  - Warren, James V. II (Text), 1960-1990 (Box 10, Folder 105)
  - Washington, Sharon Elizabeth, 1984-1987 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Waylonis, George Walter, 1961-1987 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Webb, Thomas F., 1970-1984 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Weber, Paul, 1976-1990 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Weddington, Wilburn Harold, 1978-1989 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Weilaud, Jeff, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Weiss, Harold, 1967-1988 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Weissler, Arnold M., 1960-1971 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Weller, Elizabeth Boghossian, 1985-1991 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Weller, Ron, 1985-1988 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Welling, Bradley, No Date (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Werman, Howard A., 1988 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Westra, Donald F., 1967-1980 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Whisler, Ronald, 1977-1985 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Whitcomb, Michael, 1977-1986 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Williams, J. Hutchinson, 1960-1998 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Williams, Tennyson, 1974-1990 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Williams, Tom, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Willis, Judith, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Wilson, Henry E., Jr., 1941-1981 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Wilson, Judson D., 1976-1988 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Wilson, Stephen L., 1985 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Winter, Chester Caldwell, 1961-1985 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Wise, Gary R., 1969 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Wiseman, Bruce K., 1954-1960 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Wismar, Beth Louise, 1974-1987 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Wolfe, Claire, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Wood, Jack, 1984-1991 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Wooley, Charles F., 1961-1979 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Wright, Francis, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Wright, J. Gordon, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Yashon, David, 1970-1974 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Yates, Allan J.-RESTRICTED, 1984-1988 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Yoder, Frank, No Date (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Yohn, David S., 1986-1988 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Young, Gordon A., 1965 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Young, Robert S., 1992 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Zollinger, Robert M. (1 of 3), 1960-1992 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Zollinger, Robert M. (2 of 3), 1955-1990 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Zollinger, Robert M. (3 of 3), 1967-1992 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Zollinger, Robert, 1956-1993 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Zuelzer, William (Wilhelm), 1985 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Zuspan, Frederick P., 1974-1988 (Box 11, Folder 43)